crankyape.com 2009-12-20

# Crankyape.com Bank repo rvs, motorcycles, snowmobiles, atvs, boats, trucks, trailers, go karts, jet skis, sleds, fourwheelers, trailers, motorhomes, rvs.

| 

  Search By Unit #  
  
---  
  
  Categories  

  FAQ's  

  Resources  

  Company  
  
  * [  Hours &  
  Directions](http://www.crankyape.com/default.asp?pg=hours-information)

| 

 Your Privacy

| 

* * *  
  
---  
At Midwest Recreational Clearinghouse (hereinafter referred to as “CrankyApe.com”), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process closed auctions and to provide a more personalized auction experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.   

 What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It? 

* * *  
  
---  
When you bid on an item or purchase an item at auction, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit-card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your winning auction results and to notify you of your auction sale status. 

You may voluntarily sign up to be informed about certain upcoming auctions. For this service you will need to register as a member of www.CrankyApe.com and provide a valid e-mail address, which we use to send the information you requested. 

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Web site, new CrankyApe.com services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please notify us. Make sure to notify us for each account or e-mail address you have left with us.   

 How Does CrankyApe.com Protect Customer Information? 

* * *  
  
---  
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, www.CrankyApe.com employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. If such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information on this server are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act or other law.   

 What About "Cookies"? 

* * *  
  
---  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features of our auction site, including placing items on auction and purchasing an item from someone else’s auction.   

 Will CrankyApe.com Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties? 

* * *  
  
---  
CrankyApe.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. Also, CrankyApe.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information   

 Links To Other Sites

* * *  
  
---  
Our Web site contains links to various other private organizations. Once you link to another site, you are then subject to the privacy policies of the new site. It is always a good idea to read the Privacy Policy of any site you visit.   

 In Summary 

* * *  
  
---  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make visiting [www.CrankyApe.com](http://www.crankyape.com/) possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others   

 Your Consent 

* * *  
  
---  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CrankyApe.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.   

 Tell Us What You Think?

* * *  
  
---  
CrankyApe.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please e-mail us at info@CrankyApe.com.
